atwar-game.com 2014-07-02

# Privacy policy - atWar

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. 

**We only collect anonymous information.**  
We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser) or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address. 

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you. In other words, we do not collect information such as your name, address or phone number. 

**We do not store or share your precise location.**

We do not use or collect your precise geographic location. 

**You can request to see your personal data.**

You can sign into your account to see any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name or email address. You can also contact us by email to request to see this information. 

**We keep personal data until you delete it.**

We remove personally identifiable information (email address) and other preferences associated with your account promptly after you delete your account. We may retain other data indefinitely. 

**We don't share your personal data with other companies.**  
We do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies. 

**No ad companies collect data through our service.**  
We do not allow advertising companies to collect data through our service for ad targeting. 

**You can ask privacy questions.**  
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us: dave@protobytes.net 

**Analytics providers access data on our behalf.**  
Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data. 

Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so they can improve it. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. Privacy Policy and Choices 

**We take detailed steps to protect personal information.**  
We take reasonable administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to safeguard and protect your information from unauthorized access or disclosure. This includes utilizing Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the personal information you input, and storing your information in encrypted form behind a firewall designed to block access from outside our network. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error. 

Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business. 

**Special situations may require disclosure of your data.**  
To operate the service, we also may make identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so. 

**You can review more privacy-related information.**  
This privacy policy was last updated on 11/06/13. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will make a notice on our website.
